♪The stars remember♪
♪النجوم تتذكر♪
♪The promise we made to each other♪
♪الوعد الذي قطعناه لبعضنا البعض♪
♪Every breeze carries your touch♪
♪كل نسيم يحمل لمستك♪
♪Kissing the warmth of my hand♪
♪تقبيل دفء يدي♪
♪So no matter how far it may be, don't hesitate♪
♪لذا مهما كان الأمر بعيدًا، فلا تتردد♪
♪Love will guide us through♪
♪الحب سوف يرشدنا خلال♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would I have met you a little sooner?♪
♪هل كنت سألتقي بك في وقت أقرب؟♪
♪Like night embracing the fireworks' glow♪
♪مثل الليل يحتضن توهج الألعاب النارية♪
♪You and I were meant to hold hands♪
♪لقد كان من المفترض أن نمسك أيدي بعضنا البعض♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would destiny have brought us together?♪
♪هل كان القدر سيجمعنا معًا؟♪
♪Turning thorns into silver threads on a crown♪
♪تحويل الأشواك إلى خيوط فضية على التاج♪
♪I'll weave them for you, forever around♪
♪سأنسجها لك، إلى الأبد حولك♪
=Long Planned Love=
=الحب المخطط له منذ فترة طويلة=
=Episode 13=
=الحلقة 13=
Zhou Lu,
تشو لو,
I want Jian Cheng to have me in her heart.
أريد أن أحظى بـ جيان تشنغ في قلبها.
Help me figure out a plan.
ساعدني في التوصل إلى خطة.
It's Meng Tang's stuff first.
إنها أشياء منغ تانغ أولاً.
And then it's yours.
ومن ثم يصبح لك.
Through all this, she never thought to come to me.
ورغم كل هذا، لم تفكر أبدًا في المجيء إلي.
I, as her husband,
أنا، كزوجها،
feel like I'm just a decoration.
أشعر وكأنني مجرد ديكور.
Let me give you some advice?
دعني أعطيك بعض النصائح؟
Uncle,
عم،
when did you start liking Cheng?
متى بدأت تحب تشنغ؟
It's long planned.
لقد تم التخطيط له منذ فترة طويلة.
I've finally got her.
لقد حصلت عليها أخيرا.
Since the day I stepped into the Zhou Family,
منذ اليوم الذي دخلت فيه إلى عائلة تشو،
I was placed under soft confinement by Old Master Zhou,
لقد تم وضعي تحت الحبس الناعم من قبل السيد العجوز تشو،
under the guise of protection.
تحت غطاء الحماية.
Only that little girl chasing after Zhou Yufeng
فقط تلك الفتاة الصغيرة التي تطارد تشو يوفينغ
would secretly offer me comfort when passing by my door.
كان يقدم لي الراحة سراً عندما يمر من أمام بابي.
She thought nobody ever noticed.
اعتقدت أن لا أحد لاحظ ذلك على الإطلاق.
Uncle Zhou.
العم تشو.
But she didn't know I left the door open on purpose.
لكنها لم تعلم أنني تركت الباب مفتوحا عمدا.
♪Awkwardly wiping away the tear stains♪
♪مسح بقع الدموع بطريقة محرجة♪
♪Her lips slightly move♪
♪شفتيها تتحركان قليلاً♪
♪While my heartbeat roars like thunder♪
♪بينما دقات قلبي تزمجر مثل الرعد♪
♪The heart is as fragile as glass♪
♪القلب هش كالزجاج♪
♪Longing always comes during the night♪
♪الشوق يأتي دائمًا أثناء الليل♪
♪Tears at the corner of my eyes, a trembling voice♪
♪الدموع في زاوية عيني، صوت مرتجف♪
Uncle Zhou!
العم تشو!
Uncle Zhou, wake up.
العم تشو، استيقظ.
Uncle Zhou.
العم تشو.
Hang in there.
إصمد.
I get you out of here.
سأخرجك من هنا.
If Zhou Yufeng can treat her well,
إذا كان بإمكان تشو يوفينغ معاملتها بشكل جيد،
I can keep my distance from her.
أستطيع أن أبقي مسافة بيني وبينها.
But now I've married her.
ولكن الآن تزوجتها.
I should be content.
ينبغي لي أن أكون راضيا.
But I'm greedy too.
ولكنني جشع أيضًا.
I want to be in her heart.
أريد أن أكون في قلبها.
I want her to like me a little more.
أريدها أن تحبني أكثر.
Cheng and Zhou Yufeng's bond
رابطة تشينغ وتشو يوفينغ
has been over 20 years.
لقد مر أكثر من 20 عامًا.
But so what?
ولكن ماذا في ذلك؟
She was still trampled by him.
لا تزال مدوسة من قبله.
So she is probably finding it hard
لذا فمن المحتمل أنها تجد صعوبة في ذلك
to believe in love now.
أن أؤمن بالحب الآن.
And she won't fall for someone so easily.
ولن تقع في حب شخص ما بسهولة.
That's why I come to you.
لهذا السبب أتيت إليك.
You know her well.
أنت تعرفها جيدا.
And you've got plenty of ideas.
ولديك الكثير من الأفكار.
I do have a plan.
لدي خطة.
Fight fire with fire.
حارب النار بالنار.
Let's hear it.
دعونا نسمعها.
Cheng's illness is caused by Zhou Yufeng.
مرض تشنغ سببه تشو يوفينغ.
So if you want to help her heal,
لذا إذا كنت تريد مساعدتها على الشفاء،
you'll have to start with Zhou Yufeng.
سيتعين عليك البدء مع Zhou Yufeng.
Simply put,
ببساطة،
you step over Zhou Yufeng,
لقد تجاوزت تشو يوفينغ،
and go after her.
واذهب وراءها.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Step one,
الخطوة الأولى
find a reason
إيجاد سبب
to have her come to the office
أن تأتي إلى المكتب
to have lunch with you when she's free.
لتناول الغداء معك عندما تكون متاحة.
I will create opportunities
سأخلق الفرص
for Zhou Yufeng to run into her at the company.
لكي تلتقي تشو يوفينغ بها في الشركة.
Are you helping me
هل انت تساعدني
or giving Yufeng a chance to back out?
أو إعطاء يوفينغ فرصة للتراجع؟
Never suspect the man you employ.
لا تشك أبدًا في الرجل الذي تستخدمه.
Cheng's not like other women.
تشنغ ليست مثل النساء الأخريات.
Only by flipping the script,
فقط عن طريق قلب النص،
can you actually win her over.
هل يمكنك فعلا أن تكسبها؟
No.
لا.
Stay back.
ابقى في الخلف.
Don't come closer.
لا تقترب أكثر.
- No! - Jian Cheng.
- لا! - جيان تشنغ.
Jian Cheng.
جيان تشنغ.
- No! - Wake up.
- لا! - استيقظ.
No.
لا.
- No. - Jian Cheng.
- لا. - جيان تشنغ.
Don't be scared.
لا تخف.
No.
لا.
I'm right here.
انا هنا .
It was just a dream.
لقد كان مجرد حلم.
I'll always be here for you.
سوف أكون هنا من أجلك دائمًا.
Why not wear shoes?
لماذا لا ترتدي حذاء؟
Breakfast will be ready soon.
سيكون الإفطار جاهزًا قريبًا.
Let me take you upstairs to put your shoes on.
دعني آخذك إلى الطابق العلوي لارتداء حذائك.
Thank you, Zhou Tingyan.
شكرا لك، تشو تينغيان.
Calling me honey
يناديني بالعسل
is better than saying thanks.
أفضل من قول شكرا.
Honey.
عسل.
I want to help you make breakfast.
أريد أن أساعدك في تحضير وجبة الإفطار.
Alright, alright.
حسناً حسناً.
♪Maybe the story is just too classic♪
♪ربما تكون القصة كلاسيكية للغاية♪
♪In the abyss, a garden was sown and remembered♪
♪في الهاوية، زرعت حديقة وتذكرت♪
♪In the ruins, you raise the moon, though broken♪
♪في الأنقاض، ترفع القمر، رغم أنه مكسور♪
♪I see the prophecy at dawn♪
♪أرى النبوءة عند الفجر♪
♪If the star path leads to the light-year's end♪
♪إذا كان مسار النجم يؤدي إلى نهاية السنة الضوئية♪
♪Would I have met you a little sooner?♪
♪هل كنت سألتقي بك في وقت أقرب؟♪
♪Like night embracing the fireworks' glow♪
♪مثل الليل يحتضن توهج الألعاب النارية♪
♪You and I were meant to hold hands♪
♪لقد كان من المفترض أن نمسك أيدي بعضنا البعض♪
Fang,
ناب،
can you teach me how to cook?
هل يمكنك أن تعلميني كيف أطبخ؟
Ma'am, is my cooking not good enough?
سيدتي، هل طعامي ليس جيدًا بما فيه الكفاية؟
No.
لا.
I just want to learn myself.
أريد فقط أن أتعلم بنفسي.
I want to cook for my husband.
أريد أن أطبخ لزوجي.
Ma'am, cooking is actually quite easy.
سيدتي، الطبخ في الواقع سهل جدًا.
- Sorry. - For example…
- آسف. - على سبيل المثال...
The person you are calling is busy making money.
الشخص الذي تتصل به مشغول بكسب المال.
Wait a sec.
انتظر ثانية.
- Cheng. - Yeah?
- تشنغ. - نعم؟
Are you busy?
هل أنت مشغول؟
Not now, but I will be soon. What's up?
ليس الآن، ولكن قريبًا. ما الأمر؟
I think my uncle has someone else outside.
أعتقد أن عمي لديه شخص آخر بالخارج.
Ma'am, where are you going?
سيدتي، إلى أين أنت ذاهبة؟
To fix things.
لإصلاح الأمور.
I want Jian Cheng to have me in her heart.
أريد أن أحظى بـ جيان تشنغ في قلبها.
Help me figure out a plan.
ساعدني في التوصل إلى خطة.
I do have a plan.
لدي خطة.
Fight fire with fire.
حارب النار بالنار.
Why are you dressed like this today?
لماذا ترتدي مثل هذا اليوم؟
It's not your usual style.
إنه ليس أسلوبك المعتاد.
You don't understand.
أنت لا تفهم.
When there are lots of women around,
عندما يكون هناك الكثير من النساء حولنا،
I've got to stand out.
لقد كان علي أن أبرز.
But this is your workplace.
ولكن هذا هو مكان عملك.
I need to keep it elegant.
أحتاج إلى إبقاء الأمر أنيقًا.
My face really is just too good-looking.
وجهي يبدو جميلاً جداً حقاً.
If I dress a bit more colorful,
إذا ارتديت ملابس ذات ألوان أكثر،
people think I'm just a pretty shell.
الناس يعتقدون أنني مجرد قشرة جميلة.
Seriously.
بجد.
I've got both looks and depth.
لقد حصلت على المظهر والعمق.
But what I wear doesn't really matter.
لكن ما أرتديه لا يهم حقًا.
What matters is that your uncle likes it.
المهم أن عمك يعجبه ذلك.
This style of mine
هذا أسلوبي
is exactly his taste.
هذا هو ذوقه تماما.
Yeah.
نعم.
Cheng,
تشنغ،
let me give you a heads-up.
دعني أعطيك معلومة.
Sometimes a guy likes a woman
في بعض الأحيان يحب الرجل المرأة
not just for her looks or style.
ليس فقط لمظهرها أو أسلوبها.
It's about the vibe.
إن الأمر يتعلق بالأجواء.
So what's her background exactly?
فما هي خلفيتها بالضبط؟
What does she do?
ما الذي تفعله هي؟
How old is she?
كيف القديم هو أنها؟
Is she prettier than me?
هل هي أجمل مني؟
Her background?
ما هي خلفيتها؟
She's a major client of Qianyi Group.
إنها عميلة رئيسية لمجموعة Qianyi.
Speaking of beauty...
عندما نتحدث عن الجمال...
You're the most beautiful in my eyes.
أنت الأجمل في عيني.
But
لكن
when it comes to my uncle,
عندما يتعلق الأمر بعمي،
it's hard to say.
من الصعب أن أقول ذلك.
I think my uncle treats her quite well.
أعتقد أن عمي يعاملها بشكل جيد.
You have to see for yourself.
يجب عليك أن ترى بنفسك.
(If I upset Qianyi's major client,)
(إذا أزعجت العميل الرئيسي لشركة Qianyi)
(even if Zhou Tingyan doesn't get mad,)
(حتى لو لم يغضب تشو تينغيان)
(those major shareholders tied to the group's interests)
(أولئك المساهمين الرئيسيين المرتبطين بمصالح المجموعة)
(could drown me in criticism alone.)
(يمكن أن يغرقني في النقد وحده.)
(What did I do to deserve this?)
(ماذا فعلت لأستحق هذا؟)
(My first love ran off with his secretary.)
(حبي الأول هرب مع سكرتيرته.)
(My husband got targeted by a major client.)
(تم استهداف زوجي من قبل عميل كبير.)
(Darn it!)
(لعنة عليك!)
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Hello, Mr. Zhou.
مرحباً، السيد تشو.
Remember her.
تذكرها.
This is the boss's wife.
هذه زوجة الرئيس.
From now on, let her through right away.
من الآن فصاعدا، دعها تمر على الفور.
Hello, Madam.
مرحبا سيدتي.
My clueless younger brother
أخي الأصغر الذي لا يملك أي فكرة
couldn't appreciate someone as good as Meng Tang
لا أستطيع أن أقدر شخصًا جيدًا مثل منغ تانغ
insisting on his non-marriage ideology,
أصر على أيديولوجيته بعدم الزواج،
and messing around outside.
والتسكع في الخارج.
He even ran away from home.
حتى أنه هرب من المنزل.
If you know where he is,
إذا كنت تعرف أين هو،
you have to tell me.
عليك أن تخبرني.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
What brings you here?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا؟
I…
أنا…
Cheng brought you lunch.
لقد جلب لك تشنغ الغداء.
Yeah.
نعم.
I've got something urgent to handle.
لدي شيء عاجل يجب التعامل معه.
I won't join you for lunch. I'm leaving first.
لن أنضم إليكم لتناول الغداء. سأغادر أولاً.
(So Zhou Tingyan was supposed to have lunch with that woman.)
(لذا كان من المفترض أن يتناول تشو تينغيان الغداء مع تلك المرأة.)
Come with me.
تعال معي.
Inform Zhou Yufeng come over in half an hour.
أخبر تشو يوفينغ أن يأتي خلال نصف ساعة.
Yes, sir.
نعم سيدي.
♪Late at night, I count the fleeting seconds♪
♪في وقت متأخر من الليل، أحسب الثواني العابرة♪
♪Among the crowd, I search for your gaze♪
♪بين الحشد، أبحث عن نظراتك♪
♪How deep is the secret in my heart?♪
♪ما مدى عمق السر في قلبي؟♪
♪Drawing closer under the label of friends♪
♪الاقتراب من بعضنا البعض تحت مسمى الأصدقاء♪
♪I'm afraid to disturb your peace♪
♪أخشى أن أزعج سلامك♪
♪So I protect, never daring to ask for more♪
♪لذا فأنا أحمي، ولا أجرؤ أبدًا على طلب المزيد♪
♪My eyes follow with a devotion♪
♪عيناي تتبع ذلك بإخلاص♪
♪It's the only thing I take to heart♪
♪إنه الشيء الوحيد الذي آخذه على محمل الجد♪
♪The heart is as fragile as glass♪
♪القلب هش كالزجاج♪
♪Longing always comes during the night♪
♪الشوق يأتي دائمًا أثناء الليل♪
♪Tears at the corner of my eyes, a trembling voice♪
♪الدموع في زاوية عيني، صوت مرتجف♪
♪You walk right into my dreams again♪
♪أنت تمشي مباشرة إلى أحلامي مرة أخرى♪
♪Your love is a rare luxury♪
♪حبك هو ترف نادر♪
♪So hard for me to reach♪
♪من الصعب جدًا بالنسبة لي الوصول إليه♪
♪All I can do is let it settle down♪
♪كل ما يمكنني فعله هو ترك الأمر يستقر♪
♪Back to zero♪
♪العودة إلى الصفر♪